[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：那么，让我们用链条中的承诺来练习。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So let's practice with promises in a chain.
我们要回到以前做过的同样的练习。
We're gonna go back to the same exercise that we did before.
我要你打开第三个练习，我想给你一个提示，
I want you to open up exercise three, and I want to give you the hint that,
有点像我们在练习二中所做的，getFile产生了一些东西，
kind of like what we did in exercise two where getFile produced something,
现在getFile需要产生一个承诺。
now getFile is going to need to produce a promise.
所以我们仍然要调用getFile三次。
So we're still gonna call getFile three times.
一个用于文件一，一个用于文件二，一个用于文件三。
One for file one one for file two one for file three.
我们会得到三个承诺，这是最容易的部分。
We're gonna get three promises back, that's the easy part.
我免费给你。
I'll give you that for free.
但现在你的任务是使用我刚刚教给你的
But now your task is using what I just taught you about
承诺是如何被锁在一起的。
how promises chained together.
你打算如何对这些承诺的回应进行排序？
How are you going to sequence the responses to those promises?
我们对它们进行排序的方式是将它们嵌套在一起，
In thumps the way we sequenced them was to nest them together,
但我们如何将承诺排在一起呢？
but how do we sequence promises together?
我刚刚教过你，回去看看那些幻灯片，试着练习三。
I just taught you to, go back and look at those slides and try exercise three.
只是为了确保我们在同一页上，让我打开它
Just so we make sure we're on the same page, let me open that up just so
你可以看到我们在说什么。
you can see what we're talking about.
练习三，这个getFile就在第22行，
Exercise three, this getFile right here on line 22,
这就是你需要为正在发生的事情做出承诺的地方。
that's where you need to produce a promise for what's happening.
然后我们仍然会调用getFile函数三次，然后
And then we're gonna still call the getFile function three times, and
然后我们要把这些承诺排在一起。
then we're gonna sequence those promises together.
所以让我给你五六分钟来试一试。
So let me give you five or six minutes to try your hand at that.
回去看看我刚才给你们看的最后五六张幻灯片。
Go back and look at the last five or six slides that I just showed you.
他们会告诉你如何做到这一点，所有这些步骤。
They're gonna tell you exactly how to accomplish that, all of those steps.
看看你能想出什么，然后我们几分钟后再谈。
And see what you can come up with and then we'll talk about that in a few minutes.